from prison sent to war Yes, how long did
из тюрьмы отправили на войну Да сколько
he spend in the war instead of prison he was sent to his
он на войне пробыл вместо тюрьмы его на
own place
на сво
so it turns out how many
отправили так а получается сколько он
months did he live on his own place on
месяцев прожил на сво на
his own less than
сво меньше
a month let's have a normal conversation let's have a
месяца давай нормально пообщаемся давай
normal conversation let's have a normal conversation where are you from
нормально пообщаемся давай ты откуда
baby baby Volgograd
малышка малышка Волгоград
my father is from Volgograd he said it's a
у меня отец родом из Волгограда говорил
very beautiful
очень красивый
city Yes, great, you have amulets
город Да замечательно это у тебя амулеты
against the
от
evil eye, I don't have to explain it to you directly
сглаза тебя прямо
this is nine
объяснять это девять
zy
зы
Well, this is this
Ну это
is Buddhism I can't
это это буддизм я не могу тебе сложно
explain it to you it will be difficult Why do I also have this
объяснить будет Почему я тоже это
commitment to Harki Gautama I studied
приверженность харки гаутамы Я изучал
Buddhism
буддизм
explain from the point of view of Buddhism what does this
объясни с точки зрения буддизма что это
mean Well, that is, these are certain
означает Ну то есть это определённые
stages Well, now,
стадии Ну сейчас ну
why
зачем в рамках
explain this within the framework of your dialogue with me Well,
твоего диалога со мной это объясни Ну не
we are not going to talk about politics with you
о политики же мы будем говорить с тобой
with beautiful women I am talking about
с красивыми женщинами Я говорю о
the philosophy of religion and with ugly women about
философии религии а с некрасивыми о
politics from the point of view of philosophy That
политики с точки зрения философии То
is, I adhere to everything that
есть я придерживаюсь всего то
is, if we take it as a whole I am an agnostic That
есть если взять в целом я агностик То
is,
есть
I studied the
я изучала
Christian Faith that is Well, I am
и христианскую Веру то есть Ну я
baptized, well,
крещёная вот ну
I
меня вот
have an icon I wear an icon,
есть иконка
there is an icon  I can explain what an icon
есть вот могу объяснить что такое иконка
and a small image are you know many of us say
и образок знаешь у нас многие говорят
why people wear faces people don't wear faces
зачем люди носят лица люди не носят лица
people wear an image an
люди носят образраз
image This is very different I
образок Вот это очень сильно отличается
studied the Muslim Faith I also studied
изучала мусульманскую Веру также изучала
and Judaism that is from the
и иудаизм то есть
point of view of development Buddhism is
с точки зрения развития буддизм мне
quite close to me as well as
достаточно близок так же как и
Christianity That
христианство То
is you know what an
есть ты знаешь что такое
agnostic is
агностик
perfectly well that is I accept all
отлично то есть я все
Faiths
Веры м
and try to develop from the
принимаю и стараюсь развиваться
point of view of understanding higher powers not from the
точки зрения понимая высших сил не с
point of view of God that is not a religion but
точки зрения бога то есть не религия а
Faith is not God but a higher
Вера не Бог а высшая
power Well something like
сила Ну примерно вот
this what do you
так кем
work as a sales manager in
работаете менеджер по продажам если
short and What do you sell
коротко а Что продаёте
All of you by the way also got tired of the Soviet Union
Всё вы кстати ещё Советский Союз достали
Yes I was born in eighty-first And
Да я восемьдесят первого года рождения А
what year were you And what year were you born in eighty-three
вы какого А вы какого восьмидесятого о
We are almost the same age I am 43 you are
Мы почти ровесники мне 43 вам
44 45 will be this year Well I will be 44
44 45 будет в этом году Ну мне будет 44
Yes as they say At 45 a woman is a berry
Да как говорят В 45 баба ягодка
again I don't know what happens there
опять я не знаю что там бывает
again I don't really want to realize anything so much I just
опять что-то осознавать не очень хочется
want peace
так хочется уже покоя
well you still feel like a young
просто ну вы ощущаете ещё юной
girl I don't want to feel like myself at all  I
дево Я вообще не хочу себя ощущать юной
don't want to be a young girl at all I remember myself at
девой вообще не хочу я себя вспоминаю в
and here you can swear you can
и тут Материться можно можно
Well I don't I don't want to be the person
Ну я не я не хочу быть тем человеком
I was at 20 so to speak that
которым я была в 20 лет так скажем то
is I didn't have enough of what the Lady
есть мне не хватало ни опта кем Леди
was at
были в 20
20 Well quite self-confident
лет Ну достаточно самоуверенная
crazy crazy I could
сумасшедшая чумачечая я могла там в
instantly rush from one end of the world to the other
одночасье с одного конца света в другой
somewhere I mean Well within the framework of
куда-то дёрнуть Я имею Ну в рамках
Russia In short, how can a Russian woman
России Короче как русская женщина и коня
stop a horse and enter a hot hut Yes
остановит и в горячую избу войдёт Да
yes it sounds very strange in general but
да это очень странно вообще звучит но
any It seems to me a woman not only
любая Мне кажется женщина не только
Russian and Ukrainian and Georgian
русская и украинская и грузинская
woman can stop a
женщина может остановить
horse when it is necessary That's
коня когда это следует Вот
true any nationality a woman
правда любой национальности женщина
of this if it is necessary if there is a beloved
этого если это следует если там любимый
man If there are
мужчина Если там
children there therefore no need to talk about a
дети поэтому не надо говорить про
Russian woman that she there is a lot that
русскую женщину что она там много что
can all women can absolutely everything and
может все женщины могут абсолютно все и
there is a cat accidentally on you I don't like things because
там котик случайно на вас Не налю дел а
he was so
то он так
framing you my cats it
подставлял вас смущают мои котики мне
seemed to me that he raised his tail and on you
показалось что он поднял хвост и на вас
no no not he she just jumps
нене не он она просто скачет
back and forth m and what kind of pranks are you  In our
туда-сюда м а какие шалости вы По
youth we did,
молодости делали расскажите
tell us, tell us, what pranks we
поведайте какие шалости мы
did, what
делали какие мы
pranks we did, and what exactly are pranks,
шалости А что именно под шалостей
pranks, each person has their own
шалости у каждого человека свои
pranks, it's strange, I don't know
шалости странно не знаю
honestly, I've confessed to my daughter for a long time,
честно я уже давно исповедовало даже
so
дочке своей поэтому что-то шалостей у
I don't have any pranks, nothing
меня нет ничего
like that, that's just
такого что у меня прямо вот
hidden in me, let's say, I'll put it
скрыто Ну скажем так поставлю прямо
more directly,
более прямо вопро
uh, how much did you turn the heads of young
ээ Насколько Вы вскружила головы молодым
men and not
мужчинам и не
young men again, how much did you, as a
молодым ещё раз как насколько вы будучи
young girl, turn the heads of
юной девой вскружить головы
men, Well, all sorts of things
мужчинам Ну всякое
happened, how, Well, what does it mean? Tell us
бывало как Ну что значит Расскажите
the details, that's how you seduce
детали вот как вы обольщай
men, you know. The only way to seduce a man is with
мужчин знаешь Единственное чем можно
your
обольстить мужчину - Это только своей
naturalness, this is the only way to make a man
естественностью это единственное мужчины
fall in love with your
можно влюбить только своей
naturalness. You want, what
естественностью Ты хочеш что
do you do as much as you want, you may not
делай ты сколько угодно ты можешь не
know how to eat or cook, you may not be a
уметь ни кушать готовить ты можешь быть
family man at all, but if you
никакой семейным человеком но если ты
behave naturally, either a
будешь естественно себя вести либо тебя
person will love you or he won't love you,
человек полюбит либо он тебя не полюбит
Well, you By the way, you are very natural, I would
Ну вы Кстати вы очень естественны Я бы
even say, you know,
даже сказал Знаете вы Сверхъестественная
there are Supernatural girls, they are artificial, Yes, they are
есть девушки они искусственные Да они
somehow like that, Well, out of themselves  do but you are
как-то так Ну из себя делают а вот вы
just supernatural It just
вот прям сверхъестественные Прям аж
feels
ощущается
strange what does natural mean
странно что значит естественное
supernatural
сверхъестественно
and our life in general is such a thing you even from the
и наша жизнь вообще такая вещь вы даже с
point of view of God if you
точки зрения бога если будете
listen to yourself in more you will
прислушиваться к себе в больше
understand in general how
поймёте вообще насколько
wonderful our life in general is And at what age did you
чудесная А во сколько лет вы познали
first know the joy of a
впервые радость
man I don’t remember the years probably
мужчины не помню лет наверное
1617 17 probably T there is something like that In the
1617 17 наверное Т там что-то та В
sense you don’t remember You don’t remember the
смысле не помните Вы не помните мужчину
first man I remember the first man but I don’t
первого мужчина Я первого помню но я не
remember the exact age then there were no
помню точно возраст тогда не было
cell phones and everything
сотовых телефонов и всего
else that without a hundredth phone you can’t
остального что без сотого телефона свой
know your age
возраст не узнать как
somehow Well then at least from the history of correspondence
бы не Ну тогда хоть по истории переписок
it was possible to remember okay this is a joke No of
можно было вспомнить ладно это шутка Нет
course
конечно
I remember the first man But honestly I
помню первого мужчину Но честно к нему
didn’t have any special feelings for him
особых чувств не питала
I had and have feelings for
я питала и
my last man
питаю своему последнему мужчине
and that first man and he
чувства а тот первый мужчина а он к вам
had
питал
feelings for you Well at that time probably yes there
чувства Ну на тот момент наверное да
was
страсть была там
some kind of passion there how old
какая-то сколько ему лет
was he Well about my age
было Ну примерно моего возраста
He was also
был Он тоже был
natural And how can it be
естественным А как он может быть
unnatural I generally
неестественным я вообще на тот момент
lived in Central Asia at that time so you
жила короче в Средней Азии чтобы вы
understand I won’t say the country well the
понимали не буду говорить страну ну
former country of the USSR so  let's say but in
бывшая страна СССР так скажем но в
Central Asia and he was Asian
Средней Азии и он был азиатом
Yes, he really liked me at that time,
Да я ему ну на тот момент очень
he was Tajik, Uzbek, Kyrgyz,
то он был таджик узбек киргиз
Kazakh
казах
Yes, he was Kazakh
Да он был казах
now, wouldn't you like to find
сейчас у вас не хотелось бы где-то найти
him somewhere on Odnoklassniki Have you tried to find him Well,
его в Одноклассниках не пробовали
no, my first love No, I have
найти Ну нет первую свою любовь я Нет я
n't tried to find him, probably, well, honestly, it's
не пробовала найти наверно ну честно это
not even my first love, it's such a
не даже не первая любовь это такой
first experience We met there No, I haven't
первый опыт встречались там Нет не
tried to find him,
пробовала его найти
and with whom I communicated with
а кем общалась с
the guys I
ребятами я
lived until I was 25 in Central Asia I communicated
жила до 25 лет в Средней Азии я общалась
and communicate and we communicate well and I'll
и общаюсь и прекрасно общаемся и я
say more Even some,
больше скажу Даже некоторые
uh, for a long time there Let's
ээ пуст долгое время там Давай
meet I even find it funny, they
встретимся мне прямо даже смешно такие
start to remember something old there I'm
начинают там что-то вспоминать старое я
like Wow I say it was 20 years ago
такая Ого я говорю это было 20 лет назад
and such silence I'm like, what's
и такое молчание Я такая говорю что
scary about
страшного
hearing a number I say Yes, that's how it
цифру услышать Я говорю Да вот так Это
was a long time ago I say Stop it Well,
давно было говорю Перестаньте Да ну а
look And you don't have such a feeling For
смотрите А у вас нет такого ощущения Вот
example, I once came to a
я например был приходил когда-то на
school reunion there for 10 years,
встречу выпускников школы там 10 лет
you know, in short, there are all sorts of such
знаете вот это короче там всякие такие
things Yes, and it turns out I'm looking  somehow
штуки Да и получается я смотрю как-то
everything has changed, everyone has become so creepy,
все изменили все как-то такими стрёмные
don't you have the feeling that
стали у вас нет такое ощущения что вот
these friends of yours from twenty years ago,
эти ваши друзья двадцатилетней давности
yes, now they are really some
да сейчас реально какие-то рашки они
kind of Rashki, well, at the moment we live in
такие ну на данный момент мы живём в
different countries. And with those with whom I
разных странах Вот и с теми с кем я
communicated, I still communicate with them, I correspond with someone
общалась я и общаюсь с ними с кем-то
through social networks. I even
переписываюсь через соцсети У меня даже
have one friend, Unikum, I'll tell you right
есть одна подруга Уникум я вот пря прям
now for her, really.
сечас за неё реально
In general, we lived in Baikonur,
расскажу В общем жили мы на Байконуре
so you understand, this is a territorial
чтобы вы понимали это территориальная
unit of Russia on the territory of Kazakhstan,
единица России на территории Казахстана
leased until
арендованная до
2050, so you understand. And in the
2050 года чтобы вы понимали Вот и в
end, my friend, my classmate, we
итоге моя подруга моя одноклассница мы с
studied together.
ней вместе учились
And she had a permanent residence permit on
А у неё прописка постоянная была на
the territory of
территории
Makeyevka and she had a Ukrainian passport
Макеевки и у неё был украинский паспорт
and she lived in
и она жила в
Kazakhstan and she literally
Казахстане и у неё буквально до прошлого
had a Ukrainian passport until last year. I was literally
года был украинский паспорт я прям мы с
calling her and I was laughing at her. I
ней созванивались я угорала над ней я
'm saying, I'm saying, woman. I'm
говорю я говорю женщина Я говорю вас
saying, you, I'm saying, you are aliens. I'm saying, enroll
говорю Вы инопланетяне говорю зачислять
if I say a little more and you didn't
если говорю ещё чуть-чуть и вы никак не
react at all. Last year, she received
среагировали прошлого года Она получила
Russian citizenship and
российское гражданство и от неё
all relatives refused her safely At the
отказались все родствен благополучно При
same time she says And what am I guilty of, she
этом она говорит А я в чём виновата
says I didn’t even live in Russia or in
говорит я даже не жила ни в России ни в
Ukraine, in fact, that is, she
Украине по сути то есть её от рождение
was brought there from Makeyevka to
сразу с Макеевки привезли туда на
Baikonur from birth and she lived there from birth And she
Байконур и она там от рождения жила И до
still lives and since it is a
сих пор живёт и так как это
territorial unit of Russia, she
территориальная единица России она
simply received citizenship there she
просто получила гражданство там она
tried to explain this to her relatives but her
пыталась это объяснить родственникам но
relatives did not understand her and now, as
родственники её не поняли и теперь в
a result, she found herself without relatives
итоге она оказалась и без родственников
and there Well, at least she
и там Ну по крайней мере хотя бы работу
got a job, that’s how it is in short
получила вот как-то так вкратце
And were you quite a woman in your youth
а вы в молодости были довольно женщино
or how is it now What what What again
или как сейчас что что что ещё раз Вы в
Were you happy with a woman in your youth or how is it
молодости были довольны женщиной или как
now I say You were
сейчас я говорю вы в молодости были
happy with a woman in your youth or how is it
довольны женщиной или как
now And now, how am I not wearing makeup, I’m
сейчас А сейчас как я не накрашенная
sitting at home Now you are naturally Well,
такая блин сижу дома Сейчас вы естест ну
Supernatural
Сверхъестественная
In fact, right now I have a
на самом деле сейчас у меня
pretty big
довольно-таки большая
depression
депрессия
Honestly, I have a man who
честно у меня человек безвести
went missing in
пропал на
the war and how did he get to his
войне а как он попал на сво
I don’t want to say out loud but he
Я не хочу вслух говорить но он туда
didn’t
ходить идти не
want to go there And how did
хотел А как же
Rom go I don’t want to say
пошёл Ром Я не хочу говорить
he didn't want any he went there from prison
никаких он не хотел туда он из тюрьмы
And what was he
пошёл А за что он
in prison for for
сидел за
a trifle, well, more
мелочь ну
specifically,
конкретнее
a goose, so to
гуся условно
speak And really,
говоря А реально
what Well, do
что
you want
Ну тебе хочется
content
контента
Well, I don't want to I want to know I don't want Conte
Да ну я не хочу Хочу зна Я не хочу Конте
Well, we communicated normally, so baby,
Ну мы же нормально общались так малышка
let's talk Well, normally, heart to heart
давай поговорим Ну нормально по душам
Maybe I'm a psychologist Look, I'm a
Может я психолог Смотри я вообще по
psychologist by profession yes,
профессии психолог да
I can help Come on, tell me you can't
я могу помочь Давай скажи ты не сможешь
help me maybe but at least I'll
мне помочь возможно но по крайней мере
connect your
чуть-чуть подключу твою
soul a little And you want content No, don't tell me
душу А ты хочешь контента Не не скажи
how he ended up in
как он попал в
prison he was with a friend a friend tore
тюрьму он с другом был друг сорвал у
a chain off a woman that one is not the same one he
бабы цепочку тот не тот тот рядом
stood nearby there were even cameras nearby and the
постоял там даже камеры рядом были и
cameras caught even that he didn't touch it and they still
камеры засекли даже что что не трогал и
grabbed him that's all Well, one more nuance
загребли вот и всё А ну ещё один нюанс
he's
он
a gypsy and a friend is a
цыган и друг
gypsy Yes, my husband is a gypsy And my husband's friend is also a
цыган Да мой муж цыган А друг мужа тоже
gypsy
цыган
Yes, I understand In short, they put the chain
Да понял Короче они цепочку тки посадили
in jail wallpaper wallpaper yes And what year did they put him in jail the year before last for a year they rolled him around the pre-trial
по
detention center I understand In short, when he got in,
СИЗО понял а Короче э когда вот он попал
like, from the pre-trial detention center, well  from prison they sent
типа из СИЗО его ну из тюрьмы отправили
him to war Yes, how long did he spend in the war? Not from prison they should have sent him
его Не из тюрьмы его должны
to a pretrial detention center in August last year,
были на СИЗО в августе прошлого года
but instead of
отправить в тюрьму в августе а вместо
prison they sent him to his own place,
тюрьмы его на на сво
so it turns out he
отправили так а получается сколько он
lived on
месяцев прожил на
his own for how many months? Less than
сво меньше
a month, I don’t know whether he lived or
месяца я не знаю прожил или не
not. God willing, he’s alive.
прожил Дай Бог чтобы он живой был А на
What direction was he in?
каком направлении он
South? And what do they say there at
Южный А что говорят там
the military registration and enlistment office they don’t
военкомате ничего не
say anything and they don’t pay money for him?
говорят и бабки за него не
Well, his term hasn’t expired yet.
выплачивают Ну ещё ещё срок не вышел А
How long do I have to wait to get
сколько надо прождать чтобы выплатили
money for
бабки за
him
него
for six months? Damn, we have to wait and wait. We already have to wait
полгода Блин ну надо ждать и ждать бабки
because of
нужно уже потому что
inflation, guys, I’ll give you my husband a break.
инфляция пацаны я вам отстегнуть мужа
Let’s be in on
Давайте быть в
it. Well, look, if he’s not yet like this, he did
доле Ну смотри если он ещё типа не это
n’t kinta there, like in A, yes, then maybe
не кинта нулся туда типа в А да то может
he’s in short, look. Look for Vladimir
он короче посмотри Поищи есть Владимир
Zolkin, Dmitry Apostol, maybe in short, you can
золкин Дмитро Апостол может короче можно
if he’s there. [ __ ], I’m looking everywhere, he’s
если он есть Бля я ищу везде он вообще
not a warrior at all. You see,
не воин вот понимаешь Вот человек
we have such a person. You see,
настолько у нас есть вот понимаешь
with m, there are these Tractor drivers there, you
с м там вот эти вот Трактористы там там
see, the one who goes there, he’ll be
понимаешь тот кто идёт там он будет там
making a tank there. This one  but he is definitely not a warrior
танк делать Этот но он точно не воин вот
this one he he he is
этот он он он
not well Understand he is there like such ammunition
не ну Поня он там типа такой боеприпасы
this he can yes yes yes what is he there well
вот это он может да да да что он там ну
this man did not even wear black socks
этот человек не носил даже чёрных Носков
Never he only white always white
Никогда он только белые всегда белые
always
всегда
yes And why did he go to
да А зачем он пошёл тогда
war then he was not going to Yes but he went
воевать он не собирался Да но пошёл
signed he wrote
подписал же пописал же
you mean he signed those who do not sign
ты значит он подписал кто не подписывает
remain in prison
остаются в тюрьме
I can't you I will not tell you
Я тебе не могу я не буду тебе говорить
now here I am telling you I understand
сейчас вот здесь тебе я говорю я понимаю
you are downloading your content I can't
ты качаешь свой контент я не могу тебе
tell you much
сказать многого
Although I will tell you Look he was sitting in a pre-trial
Хотя я тебе скажу Вот смотри он сидел на
detention center in
на СИЗО в
Novochek I wrote on the protection of
новочеке я написала по защите прав
human rights after the
человека после того как приехала
inspection arrived him After the inspection they send him to
проверка его После проверки отправляют в
Dagestan to Dagestan
Дагестан в Дагестан
where there are 240 people that is the usual season -
где 240 человек то есть обычное сезо -
This is somewhere around
Это где-то примерно
2500 3000 people the usual season And here in
2500 3000 человек обычное сезо А тут в
Dagestan small small Khasavyurt
Дагестан маленькая маленькая Хасавюрте
240 people what they did with them there is
240 человек что там с ними делали
unknown he called a couple of times he was there
неизвестно звонил он пару раз там был
just and only after he
просто и вот только после того как он с
returned from this Dagestan they brought him back
этого Дагестана вернулся его вернули
here and here  he signs what they
сюда и тут же он подписывает что там с
do with them there and where they are sent I'm in my
ними делают и куда их отправляют Я в
soul
душе
So you want to say that they are
То есть вы хотите сказать что их там над
abused there, beaten so that they sign
ними издеваются бьют чтобы они подписали
I know I don't know maybe they talk to them in a
знаю я не знаю может с ними
good way I don't
разговаривают и по-хорошему я не
know Well if in a good way then it means he
знаю Ну если по-хорошему значит он
signed voluntarily Well no of course voluntarily
подписал Ну нет ну конечно добровольно
of course of course no one Well you understand
конечно конечно никто Ну ты же понимаешь
what I'm
о чём я
talking about no
говорю нет
explain I didn't quite understand the
объясни Я не совсем понял тогда
logic then either voluntarily or forced
логику либо добровольно либо заставляют
but there is no other
но другого нету
no I can only assume and
нету Я могу только предполагать и
suspect as well as
подозревать так же как и
you Tell me your assumptions and
ты Расскажи свои предположения и
suspicions Well just like that a person from
подозрения Ну просто так человека с
one region to another damn in a small
одной области в другую блин в маленькое
season they will send you
сезоне отправят
understand but this is an assumption
понимаешь но это предположение Нет
No no And why then was he sent to a
нет А для чего его тогда отправили в
small season I don't know I wasn't there
маленькое сезо Я не знаю Я там не была
personally if I assume Why do you have a
лично если предположить Для чего у тебя
woman Yes you went somewhere with her with her and
баба Да ты куда-то с ней пошёл с ней а
then your wife tells you you are with her there you
потом тебе жена говорит ты с ней там ты
say
говоришь
no And who will prove whether it was or not
нет И кто докажет было это или нет
that's the same in the pre-trial detention center Well what are you laughing at And
вот так же и в СИЗО Ну а что ты ржёшь А
who there is a third pre-trial detention center will prove you  find
кто там СИЗО третий докажет ты найдёшь
someone who will prove what happened in the
того кто докажет что было в
pre-trial detention center you are such your assumption Well my
СИЗО ты такой твои предположение Ну Мои
assumptions Well you understand what I am
предположения Ну ты же понимаешь о чём я
talking about tell me frankly I don't know what is
говорю скажи ты прямо я не знаю что у
in your head that
вас в голове что
you I will not say anything frankly
вы я не буду ничего прямо говорить
I can't guess what is in your
я не могу догадаться что у вас в
head damn they took your man away in short
голове блин У вас мужика забрали короче
he disappeared somewhere and you are afraid to speak
пропал он где-то а вы боитесь говорить
damn what's the joke you are not afraid anymore
блин в чём прикол уже не боитесь
Speak as it is there is I can only
Говорите как есть есть я могу только
assume that probably the man
предположить что наверное человек
became a patriot that is why he signed and went
стал поэтому и подписал и поехал
and you are a Patriot
а вы Патриот
Roman I am not Roman I am Alexander I don't know
Роман я не роман Я Александр Я не знаю
why I am the second time Call me Roman I
почему меня второй раз Называйте Романом
apologize it is just that before I
извиняюсь просто до этого я
spoke Alexander and you are
разговаривала Александр а Вы
Elizaveta I am Olga and I simply
Елизавета я Ольга а просто я елизаветой
spoke as Elizaveta that is why you
говорил вот и
remember that Alexander you are a Patriot
запомнили так вот Александр вы Патриот
not Alexander
не Александр
Alexey I apologize again Alexey you are a
Алексей извиняюсь ещё раз Алексей вы
Patriot
Патриот
Yes and why is there an American flag behind your back then
Да а почему за вашей спиной тогда
because I am a citizen of the
американский флаг потому что я гражданин
United States of America I live in
Соединённых Штатов Америки живу в
California And you are a Patriot of which
Калифорнии А вы Патриот какой
United States of America I was born
Соединенных Штатов Америки я был родом
in Rostov when I was a patriot of Russia
из Ростова когда был патриотом России 18
I have lived for 18 years  in the USA in 2 years will be the
лет живу в США через 2 года будет
twentieth I am now a Patriot of the USA you have the
двадцатой Я теперь Патриот США у вас
location of Ukraine is this I put VN
локация Украины стоит это я ставил VN
to communicate with the Ukrainians Because
чтобы с украинцами пообщаться Потому что
if the USA is only the Americans ours
если стоит США только американцы наши
get in I also basically put it to
попадают Я тоже в принципе ставила чтобы
communicate with the Ukrainians That's true not from the
с украинцами пообщаться Вот правда не с
point of view of arguing But from the point of view
точки зрения поругаться А с точки зрения
Listen by the way I have a friend in Ukraine
Слушай у меня кстати знакомый в Украине
he works on these
есть он работает по вот этим по
prisoners of war Yes I can give him your
военнопленным Да могу ему передать ваши
name there the last name of this guy of yours
там имя фамилию вот этого парня вашего
maybe they will find out I really don't
может узнают найдут Я я очень сильно не
believe
верю
I know what I will go through
я я знаю через что я буду
and Lesh
и Лёш
I am closer to me it's easier here I will find through there
я мне ближе проще здесь я найду через
will be
будут
money if he is
деньги если он
alive I will find him How to dig up Well in the
живой я найду его Как выкопать Ну в
sense of pulling out if he is not alive
смысле вытащить если его живым нет
give me back at least something to
верните мне хотя бы то куда можно
bury But a person just you understand
захоронить Но человек просто понимаешь
one thing when a person drags for
одно дело когда человек тащит за за
something and another thing when
что-то а другое дело когда
he did not want to go for it that is not the
он не хотел идти за это то есть не в том
point that he was against it he was not a
дело что он был против он он не был
soldier
военным
at all I will say more his mother is a gypsy in
абсолютно я больше скажу у него мама на
Ukraine
Украине
That's a drama
цыганка Вот это драма
he himself it turned out that way his father took him
он он сам получилось так его отец забрал
here his father died and he  he was from an orphanage and his
сюда отец умер и он детдомовский был а
mother was there,
мать там
well, I say, they are gypsies, you understand,
ну я говорю это цыгане же понимаешь
everything is complicated,
вот всё сложно
but I, when I talk to Gami, I can say
но я я общаясь с Гами Я могу сказать
one thing, this is the only one that has
одно это единственная
no country, and probably this is conducive to
у нет стра и Наверно это располагает к
the fact that it is
тому что она
absolutely militant, that is, there is no need to
абсолютно воинственно то есть не нужно
defend either territory, anything, or one's own
защищать ни территорию ничего ни своё
sovereign, they can, yes, somewhere, something,
суверен они могут Да где-то что-то
somewhere, someone, so to speak, well, they
где-то кого-то так скажем Ну они не
will not fight with anyone, no matter what the world does
будут воевать ни с кем атно мировыми
not meet, and no matter what
не встреча И какая бы
country, any country, it doesn't matter, Ukraine,
странах любая страна неважно Украина
Russia, Spain, America, gypsies are everywhere, you name it,
Россия Испания Америка цыгане везде не
but they have no country, they have no
угодно но у них нет страны у них нет
land, and is it true that there are already
земли А это правда что там в России уже
several cases in Russia that gypsies give children away in marriage at the age of 13,
несколько случаев Что цыгане детей в 13
oh,
замуж ой
I talk to them like that, a
Я же общаюсь так с
boy, well,
ними пацан вот
he is 20 years old and he was dating
Ну ему 20 лет и он они встречались с
a girl, he is with them, it's all clans, he
девчонкой он у них же это всё кланами он
took her, stole her, in short, and she is 17 years old, so they
её Взял стырил короче а ей 17 лет так
brought him
его привлекли
in here, well, that's how it is,
здесь Ну вот так вот
somehow, I say, and they brought her in, she is almost
как-то Я говорю а е привлекли ей почти
18, there, she is literally there, in
18 там ей буквально вот там через
six months she will be with us  even well Russians
полгода будет у нас даже ну русские так
get married like that sometimes says Well dad
женятся бывает говорит Ну папа там
says something there says ki pishi dad picked her up
говорит что-то говорит ки пишу поднял её
and she quietly came for her Well that's
папа а она в тихушку за ней приехали Ну
how it's supposed to be they
так положено её
stole her so in the end dad
стырили вот в итоге папа там
was showing off there showing off they returned her back
выпендривался выпендривался её обратно
Well again Look so you
вернули Ну опять же Смотри чтоб вы
understand well really among the Gypsies it's
понимали ну реально у цыган это
approximately like among the
приблизительно как у
Slavs That is to say among the Slavs there are
славян То есть у славян есть там
Belarusians there Russians there Estonians
белорусы русские там эстонцы
there well there are quite a lot of nationalities among the Slavs so
там там ну народности у славян
you understand among the
достаточно много чтобы ты понимал у
Gypsies purely in Russia and more children of
цыган чисто в России а больше дети
nationalities
народностей
and they have an adverb
и у них есть наречие
look we study Estonian
смотри мы изучаем Эстонский язык
English there yes Russian but
английский там да русский язык но
no one studies Gypsy anywhere it
цыганский нигде никто не изучает
turns out the Gypsy language has an
оказывается у цыганского языка
adverb Well purely even
наречи Ну чисто даже
this
вот вот это
Moldovan has more or
молдаванском больше или
adverbs structure it's a separate
наречий структура это отдельная
structure I don't know why it's not
структура Я не знаю почему она не
studied there's one girl Irina I
изучается есть одна девушка Ирина её
think she is on YouTube studying
по-моему есть она в ютубер ЗНО изучает
this ZNO and she teaches children she's Ukrainian she
это и она обучает детей она украинка она
after these well
после того как вот это вот ну начались
events started she left the Russian language and
события она с русского языка ушла
switched to  English I think and
перешла на английский по-моему и на
Ukrainian so I follow her and She
украинский вот я слежу за ней и Она
tries to teach gypsy children
старается цыганских детей обучать
grammar that's just the only one I've
грамматике вот прям это единственный Я
seen a girl all over the world
вообще вот во всём мире видела
and it turns out well uh this
девушку а хорошо получается ээ вот этот
boyfriend of yours how old was he
твой парень ему сколько лет было
that your boyfriend who got into trouble
что твой парень который на сво попал
how old was he T was
сколько ему лет было Т было
he was 17 years
он меня на 17 лет
younger than me so again So you'll be
младше так ещё раз Значит тебе будет в
45 this year And he's 28 then 28 Well we've been
этом году 45 А ему значит 28 28 Да ну мы
communicating for 5 years before that
5 лет уже до этого общались
so I underestimated you And listen
с так я тебя недооценивали А слушай
can you tell me what it is he
можешь мне поведать что ж он такое
found supernatural in you I
Сверхъестественного в тебе нашёл
don't know
не знаю
Well that's just how it happened and
Ну вот так вот просто получилось так а
how did you meet look he
как вы познакомились смотри ему 23 года
was 23 when you met it
было когда вы познакомились
turns out how did we
получается как мы
meet he stole your chain Yes
познакомились он у тебя украл цепочку Да
you said either get married or I'll hand you in
ты сказала либо Женись либо сдам
open your notebook write it down in the book I'll
да открывай тетрадь записывай в книгу я
tell you how we met
тебе расскажу как мы с ним познакомились
Look I lived with my husband
Смотри я жила с мужем
8 no At that time we had probably been married for about seven years my
8 нет На тот момент наверное лет сем
husband left for a shift
было муж на вахту
then the pandemic only  first We
уехал тогда пандемия только первый У нас
started the first season of this pandemic
началась первый сезон вот этой пандемии
and he stayed on duty, he couldn't go
и он остался на вахте уехать нельзя было
home and he got stuck for 4
домой и он Застрял на 4
months, he calls me in 2020, then on
месяца звонит Он мне в 2020 году тогда
June 22, I remember it as if it were yesterday and my
22 июня это я как сейчас помню и говорит
husband says Ol says I love you, he
муж Оль говорит Я люблю тебя
says but I will live, he says with another,
говорит но буду жить говорит с другой
he says I say, he says and she is
говорит я говорит говорит и она
pregnant, in short, he took it off and there his
беременна короче он снял а там у него
rubber band broke and She got pregnant
резинка порвалась и Она забеременела
Yeah, you're kidding, so naturally I start
Ага смешно тебе вот я начинаю
looking for this girl, I found her and
естественно эту деву искать нашла её и
look at her page, there are photos of a person,
смотрю у неё на странице фотографии
I start looking for this person, I
Я начинаю этого человека искать
throw him into Google, I
закидываю в Google
look at the photo, in short, he is with a
его смотрю короче на фотографии он с
Russian woman, I find a Russian woman, I
русской женщиной нахожу русскую женщину
find a Russian woman, I don't find him, I find him on
русская женщину я я нахожу Не его нахожу
Google, as a result, in VK, this Russian woman
в Гугле В итоге в ВК русскую эту женщину
who turns out to be with him is his ex-
которая сним окажется это его бывшая
mother-in-law, Well, I understand her later, I
тёща Ну это её уже потом понимаю я
start describing the situation, don't think
начинаю описывать ситуацию не подумайте
I'm crazy, so and so, I need to
меня о сумасшедший так и так мне нужно
find this
найти этого
person, and she says I'm okay, I'll
человека а и она говорит я хорошо я ему
give him the contacts and that's it, And after that,
передам контакты и всё И вот после этого
I introduced him to him like that, stop, I
я так вот с ним познакомил стоп Я я
got lost somewhere, so your husband called,
где-то потерялся значит ваш муж позвонил
what's he, in short  his elastic band broke and
что он короче порвалась у него резинка и
he will live with another yes And then I
он с другой будет жить да А дальше я
lost contact how did you get to this one
потерял связь как вы на этого вышли
this
вышли эта
Madam was talking to a guy Well, in the end,
Мадам общалась с пацаном Ну вот в итоге
here with him,
вот с ним
here I just saw photos with him on her Instagram I
вот я просто у неё в инсте увидела с ним
screenshotted a photo through Google I found
фотки заскринил фотку через Google нашла
him I didn’t find him Or rather I found his
его его не нашла Вернее а нашла его
ex-mother-in-law there in short I found his photo with
бывшую тёщу там короче нашла его фотку с
So wait a pause so I understand So I
Так подожди пауза чтобы я понял Значит
put the accents correctly your husband
правильно расставляю акценты ваш муж
called that he
позвонил что он
took she got pregnant from him and now he will
взял она от него забеременела и он будет
live with her yes you found this one on
теперь с ней жить да вы нашли эту в
Instagram somehow through we found on
Инстаграме как-то через мы нашли в
Instagram on Instagram they found uh this
Инстаграме в Инстаграме нашли ээ этого
future husband of yours a gypsy uh they
вашего будущего мужа цыгана ээ
found his previous mother-in-law in his photo
нашли на его фотографии его предыдущую
and wrote to her mother-in-law Yes so you
тёщу и написали её тёще Да так что вы
wrote to her approximately
написали ей ей приблизительно
so you wrote Hello, I’m Olga
так что вы написали Здравствуйте я Ольга
from in short there such and such a city Yes my
из короче там такого-то города Да мой
husband is on
муж на
duty who got pregnant on her
вахте которая забеременела на неё
photos there are your ex-son-in-law Yes she
фотографии есть ваш бывший зять Да
wrote I’m saying I have such a situation my
написала Я говорю у меня такая ситуация
husband went on a spree I  need to
сложилась у меня муж загулял Мне нужно
find this one and sent a photo and that's it and
вот этого найти и фотку скинула и всё и
she laughed and said that my my
она поржал говорит говорит что мой мой
says ex-son-in-law is on
говорит бывший зять опять на
the move again I'm like Nuna says Okay I'll
кося я такая Нуна говорит Хорошо я ему
tell him and that's it Well
передам и
that's it P And why did you need to
всё Ну то есть так П А зачем вам нужно
Nati your husband Dzhakh zero in short yes And
было Нати ваш муж Джах нул короче да А
why did you need to find this guy
зачем вам надо было найти этого пацана
guy well he was on her page I
пацана ну он у неё на страниц был мне
needed to find out who she was
надо было узнать кто она
so good then mother-in-law passed on the
такая так хорошо дальше тёща передала
contact to this gypsy and well
контакт этому цыгану и ну
and well and that's it We he said go we'll
и ну и всё Мы он сказал го мы всё
solve everything she won't be with him and he says I
решим она с ним не будет и он говорит я
generally communicate with her in absentia She's
с ней вообще так по заочке общаюсь Она
cheating him in short that's it In the end he cheated me
его разводит короче вот В итоге он меня
Yes no jokes are jokes in short well
развёл Да нет шутки шутками короче
everything is there well everything is there everything
ну там всё ну там там всё
is twisted you want me to turn my soul
завернулась ты хочешь чтобы я прям душу
inside out you
на изнанку те вы
return him he has a gypsy wife He
вернула у него у него цыганская жена
had one child then as I
есть Вот у него Один дитё был потом как
found out then I met his
узнала потом я познакомилась с его
gypsy wife Wait a minute gypsy
цыганской женой Вот подожди цыганская
wife ex or she Parallel with
жена бывшая или она Параллельная с
you it turned out that parallel
тобой там получилось так что параллельно
with
со
me He has an ex-wife  because there is
мной У него есть бывшая жена потому что
also a parallel wife Yes, he lived
ещ Параллельная жена есть Да это он жил
with a Russian
с русской
girl there it turned out Well, he lived with a
девчонкой там получилось Ну жил он с
Russian girl for some time That
русской девчонкой какое-то время Вот это
was this Russian girl
и была этой русской девчонки
Mom Got it That is, the Russian girl is
Мама Понял То есть русская девчонка -
his previous one and in parallel with you there
это предыдущая его а параллельно с вами
was also the current Gypsy so yeah and
было ещ теперешнее цганская так да бы а
who Stop who is married to him who
кто Стоп кто расписан с ним кто бабки
will get the money from the
получит от
Ministry of Defense I mean money Well, if he
Минобороны В смысле бабки Ну вот если он
died Yes, most likely he died 7 million
погиб Да скорее всего он погиб 7 млн
will be paid to relatives will be received by the
выплачиватся родственникам получит
Gypsy wife or
цыганская жена или
you are not married to him neither Yani the
вы с ним никто не расписан ни Яни
Gypsy wife that is the mother
цыганская жена то есть мама
will receive the mother especially will not receive He is from an
получит мама тем более не получит Он же
orphanage in the sense in general
детдомовский в смысле вообще бабки на
no one will get money down the drain No, he has omn what what what what
ветер никто не получит Нет у него омн
he has he has his
что что у него что у него у него На него
son is registered in his name Well, that means in the name of the son sweat
сын оформлен А ну всё Значит на сына пот
that is the Gypsy wife will take it
то есть цыганская жена заберёт
Well, I communicate with her every day I
Да ну я с ней общаюсь каждый день
communicate Yes, the son of the Gypsy wife is from him
общаюсь Да сын у цыганской жены от него
so yes yes that is 7 million will go to the Gypsies
так да да то есть 7 млн пойдёт цыганам
Why  seven A how many A how many
Почему сем А сколько А сколько
13 Well already 13 cool well okay
13 Ну уже 13 прикольно ну нормально
I'll raise Well I don't I hope that he
подниму Ну я не Я надеюсь что он живой
comes back alive
вернётся
I hope I know
Надеюсь я зна знаю
him not Hang out baby will
его не Зависай малыш
remain This story is
останется Эта история
unsaid Indian film will continue
недосказано индийский фильм продолжится
in the next program Yes in the next
в следующей передачи Да в следующей
episode
серии
I will not comment on anything It
я не буду ничего комментировать Походу
seems that here we will say everything to comment This will only
всё скажем комментировать Это только
spoil from you I only require a like
портить от вас только требую лайк
subscribe comment and send to friends here
подписка комент и скиньте друзьям вот
send Let them
скиньте Пусть они
with you Girls, you are worried that you are not
у вас Девушки вы переживаете что вы
beautiful enough or that you do not have a
недостаточно или красивы что у вас нет
man
мужчины
Find your ex-husband on Instagram her
Найдите в инсте своего бывшего мужика
girlfriend Find some
подругу у неё Найдите там какого-то
guy there Find t and Write to
мужика Найдите т и Напишите
him like subscribe comment subscribe to y
ему лайк подписка комент подпишись на й
Telegram right now ovin and while
Telegram прям зараз овин а пок
very and very important YouTube Zaga us
дуже и дуже важливо YouTube Зага нас
through scarg or in your ban and very many
через скарг ор в твый бан и дуже багато
videos I do not show people at times I do not show
вдео не показую людям вчасно не показуе
information about streams That is why
информация про стрими Тому для того щоб
we Mali prompt connection  write
ми Мали оперативний звязок пишиться
right now and while there in telegram okrim
прямо зараз а пок там в телегра окрим
video also interesting and useful information
видео ще теж цикава и корисна информация
and we owe you trima
и мы повинни вами трима
constant operational connection
постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that che will show you about this
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine write
YouTube Слава украини пиши